Guide to the Public Art Fund Archive MSS.270
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XI: Film
  - "DFF" - Reel 3 - Pix, undated (Reel 270.0277)
  - "DFF" - Reel 3 - Mag Track, undated (Reel 270.0278)
  - "DFF" - Reel 4 - Pix, undated (Reel 270.0279)
  - "DFF" - Reel 4 - Mag Track, undated (Reel 270.0280)
  - "DFF" - Reel 5 - Pix, undated (Reel 270.0281)
  - "DFF" - Reel 5 - Mag Track, undated (Reel 270.0282)
  - "DFF" - Reel 6 - Pix, undated (Reel 270.0283)
  - "DFF" - Reel 6 - Mag Track, undated (Reel 270.0284)
  - PAF Portraits - 30th Anniversary Video - F1, undated (Reel 270.0285)
  - PAF Portraits - 30th Anniversary Video - F1, undated (Reel 270.0286)
  - "DFF" - DIAL A, undated (Reel 270.0287)
  - "DFF" - DIAL B, undated (Reel 270.0288)
  - "DFF" - Slop Print (B&W Print) - Pix, undated (Reel 270.0289)
  - "DFF" - Music A, undated (Reel 270.0290)
  - "DFF" - Fx A, undated (Reel 270.0291)
  - "DFF" - Fx B, undated (Reel 270.0292)
  - "DFF" - Work Pix, undated (Reel 270.0293 - 270.0294, Media ID: 270.0293)
  - "DFF" - Unidentified Element, undated (Reel 270.0293 - 270.0294, Media ID: 270.0294)
  - "DFF" - Nevelson" MOS, undated (Reel 270.0295 - 270.0297, Media ID: 270.0295)
  - "DFF" - "Rosenthal" MOS, undated (Reel 270.0295 - 270.0297, Media ID: 270.0296)
  - "DFF" - "Murals/Sculpture/Peo" MOS, undated (Reel 270.0295 - 270.0297, Media ID: 270.0297)
  - "DFF" - Misc. Buildings/Peo" MOS, undated (Reel 270.0298 - 270.0301, Media ID: 270.0298)
  - "DFF" - "G.A. Plaza" MOS, undated (Reel 270.0298 - 270.0301, Media ID: 270.0299)
  - "DFF" - "Select City" MOS, undated (Reel 270.0298 - 270.0301, Media ID: 270.0300)
  - "DFF" - "City Select" MOS, undated (Reel 270.0298 - 270.0301, Media ID: 270.0301)
  - "DFF" - "City From Rooftop" MOS, undated (Reel 270.0302 - 270.0304, Media ID: 270.0302)
  - "DFF" - "Haas" MOS, undated (Reel 270.0302 - 270.0304, Media ID: 270.0303)
  - "DFF" - "Cube/Nevelson Plaza" MOS, undated (Reel 270.0302 - 270.0304, Media ID: 270.0304)
  - "DFF" - "Intv. Select #1", undated (Reel 270.0305)
  - "DFF" - "Intv. Select #2", undated (Reel 270.0306)
  - "DFF" - "Intv. Select #3", undated (Reel 270.0307)
  - "DFF" - "Intv. Select #4", undated (Reel 270.0308)
  - "DFF" - "Music" - "Outs", undated (Reel 270.0309)
  - "DFF" - "new Deal Films/EFX", undated (Reel 270.0310)
  - "DFF" - "Slides", undated (Reel 270.0311)
  - "DFF" - "Trims and Outs", undated (Reel 270.0312)
- Series XII: Audio
  This series contains audio recordings from the Public Art Fund Archive. The audio consists of recordings of lectures, panel discussions, interviews, news broadcasts, community hearings, and audio used as source material. The Audio reels titled "New Deal Films" correspond to a 16mm film, titled "Towards a Livable City" (Media ID 270.032 - Media ID: 270.0335) Descriptions are derived from the original cassette or container annotations and include title, date, the original format of audio, and the total running time (TRT).
  - Steve Carter Sept 18, 1970 / Mon Levinson Nov. 27 1970 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0314)
    Format: 1/4" audiocassette
  - Lehman Collage - Public Art symposium - Dec 14 1971 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0315)
  - Artist Community Meeting - Jan 11, 1972 - Planning Sculpture Neighborhood Exhibition (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0316)
  - City Walls 3/24/73, 1973 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0317)
  - Nina Grad '73, 1973 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0318)
  - Smithtown - Community Presentation, 1976 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0319)
  - Freedman Dedication Gallery, 1976 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0320)
  - Art Commission Meeting '78, 1978 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0321)
  - Sale Message, [1978] (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0322)
  - D.C.F - Philadelphia Museum/Public Art-City Walls - 4/27/79, 1979 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0323)
  - New Deal - 191426 / New Deal Films: "DFF" 2/82 - SR 6 Richard Haas in studio/ Tony Rosenthal in Astor Place, 1982 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0324)
  - New Deal Films: "DFF" 3/82 - SR 9 Kenneth Snelson in studio/ T. Rosenthal; Kent Barwick Central Park, 1982 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0325)
  - New Deal Films Inc. / Camera 1+2+3 Susan Randolph/Brendan Gill, 1982 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0326)
  - New Deal Films Inc. / March 9, 1982 / Louise Nevelson Interview/ Sound Roll 4 Camera Roll 6 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0327)
  - New Deal Films Inc. / Camera Roll 8+9/Sound Roll 5/ August Heckscher / John Lindsey/ March 9, 1982 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0328)
  - New Deal Films Inc. / Paul Goldberger / Sound Roll [1 2 1]/ Camera Roll [3+4+1], 1982 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0329)
  - New Deal Films Inc. / March 8, 1982 / Sound Roll 3 / Camera Roll 5 / Paul Goldberger / Mayor Koch (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0330)
  - New Deal Films Inc. / Sound Roll 6 - 3/11/82 - D.F.F. / 71/2ips 60 HZ / 24 FPS 16mm stock sound #24-, 1982 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0331)
  - New Deal Films Inc. / Roll 7 / Richard Haas ext- / Tony Rosenthal ", 1982 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0332)
  - New Deal Films Inc. / Roll 8, 1982 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0333)
  - New Deal Films Inc. / Roll 9, 1982 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0334)
  - New Deal Films Inc. - Mark di Suvero - (Doris Freedman) [Long Island City], April 5, 1982; cuid43950 (Box 104, Audiocassette ID: 270.0335)
    Duration: 6 min.
  - Hearing on relocation of Richard Serra Sculpture at 26 Federal Plaza, 1984 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0336)
  - Community hearing re: Richard Serra sculpture at 26 federal Plaza/Foley square, 1984 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0337)
  - Art in NYC ME 871127, 1987 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0338)
  - Cologne/San Francisco Soundbridge / Sound sculptures by Bill Fontana / May 31, 1987 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0339)
  - N.P.R. Weekend Edition #870426 6 mins. "Messages to the Public Alfredo Jaar / Public Art Fund / 4.26.87, 1987 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0340)
  - Public Art Fund - Spectacolor billboard 1989 November / 800 Buy with Art (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0341)
  - the MAS Fellows / Art in Public Spaces: Its Use + Abuse, 1990 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0342)
  - WE 870426 / Art in Times Square, 1990 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0343)
  - The new old west / ATC 900723, 1990 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0344)
  - Fontana: NY Harbor (NY harbor, SF soundbridge), 1991 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0345)
  - Bill Fontana - NY Harbor Gong Buoy, 1991 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0346)
  - Benefit Speeches 6/6/91 (microcassette), 1991 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0347)
  - Fontana: NY Harbor Bell Buoy, 1991 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0348)
  - Public Art Fund [WQCD] - Nancy Newhouse - 6/16/91 / Susan Freedman/ Robert Ressler, 1991 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0349)
  - Charted Collected and Carefully counted / Interview: Nicole R. [Akiesa Griffith], 1992 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0350)
  - A Day Without Art / News Report aired on WBAI FM / December 1, 1992 / Produced by David Sears, 270.0351 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0351, E-records fales_mss270, E-records 270.0351)
    Format: 1/4" audiocassette, Duration: 12 min. Side two is blank.
  - Trans- Voices sample tape - not for broadcast, 1992 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0352)
    TRT: 00:25:00
  - Missing in Action / Public Art 3/23/93 #1, 1993 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0353)
  - Missing in Action Public Art 3/23/93 #2, 1993 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0354)
  - WNYC - July 22, 1993 / James Clark, Harriet [Seuie], Melinda Hunt (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0355)
  - Botero in New York / WNCN - FN, 9/25/93 10:55 AM // Side B: Judith Shea Interview WNCN '93, 1993 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0356)
  - 11/7/95 Tom Finkelpearl - Tuesday Night Talks, 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0357)
  - Tuesday Night Talks - Tom Finkelpearl 11/7/95, 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0358)
  - 11/14/95 Vito Acconci - Tuesday Night Talks, 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0359)
  - Tuesday Night Talks / Vito Acconci - 11/14/95 - Tape 1, 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0360)
  - Tuesday Night Talks / Vito Acconci - 11/14/95 - Tape 2, 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0361)
  - 11/21/95 Kristin Jones / Andrew Ginzel / Tuesday Night Talks, 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0362)
  - Tuesday Night Talks / Kristin Jones / Andrew Ginzel / 11/21/95 - 9327-4, 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0363)
  - 11/28/95 - Tom Otterness - Tuesday Night Talks, 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0364)
  - Tuesday night talks / Tom Otterness - 11/25/95, 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0365)
  - "What They Remember" - Composite (7:16) Public Art Fund inc. 05/05/95, 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0366)
    TRT: 00:07:16
  - "What They Remember" - Continuous 1kHz test tone. Pubic Art Fund inc. 05/05/95, 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0367)
  - "What They Remember" - Continuous 1kHz test tone. Pubic Art Fund inc. 05/05/95, 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0368)
  - "What They Remember" - Composite (7:16) Public Art Fund inc. 05/05/95, 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0369)
  - "What They Remember" - Dara Kenigsberg (2:17) Public Art Fund Inc. 05/05/95, 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0370)
  - "What They Remember" - Dara Kenigsberg (2:17) Public Art Fund Inc. 05/05/95, 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0371)
  - "What They Remember" - Ruthie Mirsky (7:53) Public Art Fund Inc. 05/05/95, 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0372)
    TRT: 00:07:53
  - "What They Remember" - Ruthie Mirsky (7:53) Public Art Fund Inc. 05/05/95, 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0373)
  - "What They Remember" - Sam Chen (3:35) Public Art Fund Inc. 05/05/95, 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0374)
    TRT: 00:03:35
  - "What They Remember" - Sarah Finkelstein (8:00) Public Art Fund Inc. 05/05/95, 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0375)
    TRT: 00:08:00
  - "What They Remember" - Yuri & Yana Abayev (5:04) Public Art Fund Inc. 05/05/95, 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0376)
    TRT: 00:05:04
  - "What They Remember" - Yuri & Yana Abayev (5:04) Public Art Fund Inc. 05/05/95, 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0377)
  - [2/95 GERZ], 1995 (Box 105, Audiocassette ID: 270.0378)
  - [Eldridge street synagogue Yuri and Yana Abayer / Tatiana Shamayera/ Rafael Borukhov], 1995 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0379)
  - "What They Remember" MASTER Public Art Fund, 1995 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0380)
  - "What They Remember" MASTER, 1995 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0381)
  - Tuesday Night Talks / Judith Shea - 3/26/96, 1996 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0382)
  - 3/26/96 JUDITH SHEA -Tuesday Night Talks, 1996 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0383)
  - Rachel Whiteread - May 8, 1996 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0384)
  - Tuesday Night Talks / Rachel Whiteread - May 8, 1996 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0385)
  - Magdalena Abakanowicz - Tuesday Night Talks - 9/17/96, 1996 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0386)
  - Magdalena Abakanowicz - September, 17, 1996 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0387)
  - Tuesday Night Talks - 10/15/96 - Mary Jane Jacob, 1996 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0388)
  - Mary Jane Jacob - October 15, 1996 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0389)
  - Wodiczko, Krzysztof - 29 October 1996 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0390)
  - Wodiczko, Krzysztof - October 29, 1996 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0391)
  - Gregnik Proto II by Gregory Green, 1996 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0392)
  - Gregnik Proto I - tape 1, 1996 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0393)
  - Gregnik Proto I - tape 2, 1996 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0394)
  - Gregnik Proto I - tape 3, 1996 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0395)
  - Tuesday Night Talk: Ilya Kabakov / March 11, 1997 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0396)
  - Ilya Kabakov / March 11, 1997 / 9627-5 / Public Art Fund - Tuesday Night Talks at The Cooper Union / March - April - May 1997 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0397)
  - König, Kasper / April 1 1997 / Public Art Fund - Tuesday Night Talks at The Cooper Union / March - April - May 1997 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0398)
  - König, Kasper - 4/1/1997 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0399)
  - Komar & Melamid / 15 April 1997 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0400)
  - Komar & Melamid / April 15, 1997 /Public Art Fund / Tuesday Night Talks at The Cooper Union / March - April - May 1997 / 10559-5 (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette ID: 270.0401)
  - Alison Saar & Betye Saar - 15 May 1997 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0402)
  - Alison Saar & Betye Saar - May 15, 1997 / Public Art Fund - Tuesday Night Talks at The Cooper Union-March-April-May 1997/10559-3 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0403)
  - Grennan and Sperandio - Tuesday Night Talk: Sept 1997 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0404)
  - Grennan and Sperandio - Public Art Fund - Tuesday Night Talks at The Cooper Union-Fall 1997/10559-2 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0405)
  - Gregory Green - October 2, 1997 / Public Art Fund-Tuesday Night Talks at The Cooper Union-Fall 1997/10559-1 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0406)
  - Gregory Green - October 7, 1997 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0407)
  - Eleanor Heartney - 10/21/97, 1997 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0408)
  - Eleanor Heartney - October 27, 1997 / Public Art Fund - Tuesday Night Talks at The Cooper Union-Fall 1997/10772-2 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0409)
  - Andrea Zittel Fall 1997 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0410)
  - Andrea Zittel / Public Art Fund - Tuesday Night Talks at The Cooper Union-Fall 1997/10772-5 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0411)
  - Mark Dion 31 March 1998 / Tuesday Night Talks (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0412)
  - Mark Dion March 31, 1998 / Public Art Fund - Tuesday Night Talks at The Cooper Union (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0413)
  - Public Art Fund - Rachel Whiteread - 9/15/98, 1998 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0414)
  - Shimon Attie, 1998 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0415)
  - Shimon Attie c. 1998 / Public Art Fund - Tuesday Night Talks at The Cooper Union (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0416)
  - Gabriel Orozco c. 1998 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0417)
  - Gabriel Orozco c. 1998 / Public Art Fund - Tuesday Night Talks at The Cooper Union (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0418)
  - Ann Hamilton Sept 28, 1999 / 10825-5 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0419)
  - Pipilotti Rist / October 5th, 1999 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0420)
  - Pipilotti Rist / Tuesday October 5th, 1999 / Public Art Fund - Tuesday Night Talks at The Cooper Union (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0421)
  - Matthew Barney, 1999 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0422)
  - Matthew Barney / Tuesday October 19th, 1999 / Matthew Barney / Public Art fund / Tuesday Night Talks at The Cooper Union / 10772-4 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0423)
  - WNYC AM820 / 93.9FM / Eccles / Oursler, 2000 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0424)
  - Public Art Fund / Jeff Koons / Dog Sculpture, 2000 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0425)
  - "Public Art Fund / Video Images Project" - Sunday PM / 9-24-00, 2000 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0426)
    TRT: 00:01:02
  - "Rockefeller Plaza Spider exhibit", 2001 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0427)
  - Maurizio Cattelan (copy) - 10/9/01, 2001 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0428)
  - Shirin Neshat (copy) - 10/23/01, 2001 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0429)
  - Public Art Fund / 3-12-02, 2002 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0430)
  - Public Art Fund - AD Special Programs-1 of 2 / 3-26-02, 2002 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0431)
  - Public Art Fund - AD Special Programs-2 of 2 / 3-26-02, 2002 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0432)
  - Public Art Fund - Vik Muniz - April 9, 2002 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0433)
  - Vik Muniz - April 9, 2002 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0434)
  - Public Art Fund - Vik Muniz - April 9, 2002 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0435)
  - NPR All Things Considered / 6-14-02, 2002 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0436)
  - Mariko Mori - 10/8/02, 2002 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0437)
  - Public Art Fund - Janet + Louise Wilson - Oct 22, 2002 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0438)
  - Takashi Murakami - AD Special Programs / 4-15-03 / Copy, 2003 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0439)
  - Takashi Murakami - AD Special Programs / 4-15-03 / Copy, 2003 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0440)
  - Public Art Fund - 1 of 1 - 3/25/03, 2003 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0441)
  - Vanessa Beecroft - AD Special programs / 5-13-03, 2003 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0442)
  - Tom Sach - AD Special Programs - 10/28/03, 2003 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0443)
  - Tiravanija, Rirkrit - AD Special Programs / 11-04-03, 2003 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0444)
  - Public Art Fund Lecture - [Matthew Richie] 3/30/04, 2004 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0445)
  - Public Art Fund Lecture - Dijkstra, Reneke - 4/3/04, 2004 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0446)
  - Public Art Fund: McCarthy - April 27 2004 / Copy (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0447)
  - Public Art Fund: Alÿs, Francis - AD Special Programs / 1104094, 2004 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0448)
  - Public Art Fund: Janet Cardiff - Adult Special Programs - 1 of 2, 2004; cuid39241 (Box 106, Audiocassette ID: 270.0449)
    Duration: 49 minutes
  - Public Art Fund: Janet Cardiff - Adult Special Programs - 2 of 2, 2004; cuid39242 (Box 106, Audiocassette ID: 270.0450)
    Duration: 6 minutes
  - Public Art Fund: Huyghe, Pierre - Adult Special Programs - 2 of 2, 2004 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0452)
  - Public Art Fund: Sarah Morris - NSU Mar. 8, 2005 -copy (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0453)
  - Public Art Fund: Eliasson, Olafur - NSU - Mar. 29, 2005, 1 of 2 / 19978-1 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0454)
  - Public Art Fund: Eliasson, Olafur - NSU - Mar. 29, 2005, 2 of 2 / 19978-1 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0455)
  - Public Art Fund: Edmier, Keith - NSU - April 5, 2005 - copy / 19978-3 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0456)
  - Public Art Fund #1 - [Roni Horn] - 11/07/05, 2005 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0457)
  - Public Art Fund - 12/5/05 - Josiah McElheny - copy, 2005 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0458)
  - Public Art Fund - Do-Ho Suh - 11/21/05 - copy, 2005 (Box 106, Media ID: 270.0459)
  - WNYC NY Beat - 10/29/96 / 2006-2100 (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0460)
  - PAF John Currin - John Currin - March 28 06, 2006 (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0461)
  - Rodney Graham - April 18 06 - 1 of 2, 2006 (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0462)
  - Rodney Graham - April 18 06 - 2 of 2, 2006 (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0463)
  - Public Art Fund #6 - Sarah Sze - 5/2/06 - copy, 2006 (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0464)
  - Dan Graham Dupe-Public Art Fund 1 of 2 / 10-24-06 / copy, 2006 (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0465)
  - [Dan Graham] Public Art Fund - 2 of 2, 2006 (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0466)
  - Public Art Fund - Sharon Lockhart - 11/7/06 - AD Special Programs - 1 of 2, 2006 (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0467)
  - Public Art Fund - Sharon Lockhart - 11/7/06 - AD Special Programs - 2 of 2, 2006 (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0468)
  - Public Art Fund - [Sean Landers] / 11-21-06, 2006 (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0469)
  - Public Art Fund - dub - Dan Graham - NS - October 24, 2006 - 1 of 2 (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0470)
  - Public Art Fund - NS VLC ALEX KATZ April 4, 2007 (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0471)
  - Charles Ray - AD Special Programs - 4/18/07, 2007 (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0472)
  - Yuskavage, Lisa / Public Art Fund / AD Special Programs - 1 of 1 / 5-3-07 / copy, 2007 (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0473)
  - Joo, Michael / AD Special Programs - Tishman Auditorium / 10-3-07, 2007 (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0474)
  - Public Art Fund #2 - Tishman Auditorium - Phoebe Washburn / 10-24-07, 2007 (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0475)
  - Public Art Fund @NS - Stan Douglas-Film+Video-copy-Nov 7, 2007 (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0476)
  - Paul Chan VLC (Public Art Fund) 4-30-08 Copy, 2008 (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0477)
  - NS-VLC Public Art Fund / November 5, 2008 - 1 of 2 (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0478)
  - NS-VLC Public Art Fund / November 5, 2008 - 2 of 2 (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0479)
  - Public Art Fund / 11-19-08 - Catherine Sullivan - 54527-3, 2008 (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0480)
  - [Heschel School - 1. Dan Janvey, 2. Effie Pellet], undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0481)
  - Tape #1 -- Eldridge Street #1, undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0482)
  - Tape #2 -- Eldridge Street #2, undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0483)
  - Tape #3 Ramaz School, undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0484)
  - Tape #4 - [Heschel School], undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0485)
  - Andre Schub, undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0486)
  - Answering Machine - incoming messages, undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0487)
  - Answering machine tape - Public Art Fund, undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0488)
  - Answering machine message - Nina Freedman, undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0489)
  - Amy Eddings - "tourguide" -7/16, undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0490)
  - Cassette machine instruction, undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0491)
  - Community Board #7 - re: West Side Waterfront Development, undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0492)
  - Computron - 1 + 2, undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0493)
  - Computron - 3 + [4], undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0494)
  - Computron - 3 + 4 (New Deal 191346), undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0495)
  - Computron - 5 + 6, undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0496)
  - Computron - 7 + 8, undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0497)
  - DFF 1 + 2 - Transcription Cassette 1st Shooting Day (New Deal 191346), undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0498)
  - DFF 3 + 4 - (New Deal 191346), undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0499)
  - DFF 5, undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0500)
  - "Fresh Air" - Chain Reaction - Lynn Hershman [1983?], undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0501)
  - Graduation Ceremony - (Karen), undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0502)
  - Interviews Tape #1 / Public Art Fund, undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0503)
  - Interviews Tape #2 / Public Art Fund, undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0504)
  - Interviews Tape #3 / Public Art Fund, undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0505)
  - Interview - Doris Freedman IRS Building, undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0506)
  - Joanna Morris interviews Susan K. Freedman, undated; cuid43951 (Box 107, Audiocassette ID: 270.0507)
    Duration: 60 minutes; Preservation Note: Speed and pitch problems on side 2.
    Joanna Morris interviews Susan K. Freedman, President of the Public Art Fund. Topics discussed include the Public Art Fund's goals, history, operations, and projects.
  - Doris Freedman interviews Karen Bacon, undated; cuid43952 (Box 107, Audiocassette ID: 270.0508)
    Duration: 4 minutes; Preservation Note: Speed and pitch problems on side 1; some minor adjustments were made. Side 2 is blank.
    This recording includes a discussion of the Red Groom "Rockus Manhattan" exhibition opening.
  - Doris Freedman interviews, undated; cuid43953 (Box 107, Audiocassette ID: 270.0509)
    Duration: 43 minutes; Preservation note: Multiple blank sections removed from side 2 for the access copy.
    Doris Freedman interviews pedestrians about the Mark Di Suvero Battery Park sculpture; Nancy Kaufman, Director of the visual arts referral services of the Creative Artists Public Service Program (CAPS); artist Richard Haas; and Sarah Garretson of NYC's Cultural Council Foundation.
  - Doris Freedman interviews, undated; cuid43954 (Box 107, Audiocassette ID: 270.0510)
    Duration: 50 minutes; Preservation Note: Poor audio on side 1.
    Doris Freedman interviews David Rockefeller, President of the Associated Council on the Arts (ACA); Bob Maurer, artist; Wallace West, Executive Director of the Queens Council on the Arts; Doris M, Nebraska artist representative; and Muriel Silberstein of the NYC Arts Commision. Topics discussed include the history and operations of the ACA Annual Conference, commissioning programs for artists, and public sculpture.
  - Interview with child (Tape #1 Dub), undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0511)
  - I.S. talking about Henry -[Doris Birth], undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0512)
  - Kabakov - Lost glove p.r. from NPR, undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0513)
  - Kabakov Master, undated (Box 107, Media ID: 270.0514)